<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TelegramClone</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="hint_chat_edittext">Write a message</string>

    <string name="test_string">She suspicion dejection saw instantly.
        Well deny may real one told yet saw hard dear.
        Bed chief house rapid right the. Set noisy one state tears which. No girl oh part must fact high my he.
        Simplicity in excellence melancholy as remarkably discovered.
        Own partiality motionless was old excellence she inquietude contrasted.
        Sister giving so wicket cousin of an he rather marked. Of on game part body rich. Adapted mr savings venture it or comfort affixed friends.
Your it to gave life whom as. Favourable dissimilar resolution led
        for and had. At play much to time four many. Moonlight of situation so if necessary therefore attending abilities.
        Calling looking enquire up me to in removal. Park fat she nor does play deal our.
        Procured sex material his offering humanity laughing moderate can.
        Unreserved had she nay dissimilar admiration interested.
        Departure performed exquisite rapturous so ye me resources. </string>

    <string name="test_string_big">Talking chamber as shewing an it minutes. Trees fully of blind do. Exquisite favourite at do extensive listening. Improve up musical welcome he. Gay attended vicinity prepared now diverted. Esteems it ye sending reached as. Longer lively her design settle tastes advice mrs off who.

Projecting surrounded literature yet delightful alteration but bed men. Open are from long why cold. If must snug by upon sang loud left. As me do preference entreaties compliment motionless ye literature. Day behaviour explained law remainder. Produce can cousins account you pasture. Peculiar delicate an pleasant provided do perceive.

As it so contrasted oh estimating instrument. Size like body some one had. Are conduct viewing boy minutes warrant expense. Tolerably behaviour may admitting daughters offending her ask own. Praise effect wishes change way and any wanted. Lively use looked latter regard had. Do he it part more last in. Merits ye if mr narrow points. Melancholy particular devonshire alteration it favourable appearance up.

Stronger unpacked felicity to of mistaken. Fanny at wrong table ye in. Be on easily cannot innate in lasted months on. Differed and and felicity steepest mrs age outweigh. Opinions learning likewise daughter now age outweigh. Raptures stanhill my greatest mistaken or exercise he on although. Discourse otherwise disposing as it of strangers forfeited deficient.

Is post each that just leaf no. He connection interested so we an sympathize advantages. To said is it shed want do. Occasional middletons everything so to. Have spot part for his quit may. Enable it is square my an regard. Often merit stuff first oh up hills as he. Servants contempt as although addition dashwood is procured. Interest in yourself an do of numerous feelings cheerful confined.

Meant balls it if up doubt small purse. Required his you put the outlived answered position. An pleasure exertion if believed provided to. All led out world these music while asked. Paid mind even sons does he door no. Attended overcame repeated it is perceive marianne in. In am think on style child of. Servants moreover in sensible he it ye possible.

Left till here away at to whom past. Feelings laughing at no wondered repeated provided finished. It acceptance thoroughly my advantages everything as. Are projecting inquietude affronting preference saw who. Marry of am do avoid ample as. Old disposal followed she ignorant desirous two has. Called played entire roused though for one too. He into walk roof made tall cold he. Feelings way likewise addition wandered contempt bed indulged.

Guest it he tears aware as. Make my no cold of need. He been past in by my hard. Warmly thrown oh he common future. Otherwise concealed favourite frankness on be at dashwoods defective at. Sympathize interested simplicity at do projecting increasing terminated. As edward settle limits at in.

Picture removal detract earnest is by. Esteems met joy attempt way clothes yet demesne tedious. Replying an marianne do it an entrance advanced. Two dare say play when hold. Required bringing me material stanhill jointure is as he. Mutual indeed yet her living result matter him bed whence.

Dwelling and speedily ignorant any steepest. Admiration instrument affronting invitation reasonably up do of prosperous in. Shy saw declared age debating ecstatic man. Call in so want pure rank am dear were. Remarkably to continuing in surrounded diminution on. In unfeeling existence objection immediate repulsive on he in. Imprudence comparison uncommonly me he difficulty diminution resolution. Likewise proposal differed scarcely dwelling as on raillery. September few dependent extremity own continued and ten prevailed attending. Early to weeks we could. </string>

    <string-array name="cam_options">
        <item>From camera</item>
        <item>From gallery</item>
        <item>Delete photo</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="invitation_text">Hey, I\'m using Telegram to chat. Join me! Download it here: https://telegram.org/dl</string>

</resources>
